THREATENED BY A RUTELESS DEMON, HUMANITY WAS ON THE BREAK OF DESTRUCTION.
ALL SEEMED LOST UNTIL A LONE MAGE STEPPED FORWARD AND TOOK UP THE FIGHT.
THE HERO'S NAME WAS LUMIERE SILVER MILLION CLOVER.
HE WAS LATER HAILED AS THE FIRST WIZARD KING, AND HIS STORY BECAME LEGEND.
FANTASTIC, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING, AND OUR KING!
風が背中を張ってシスクは糸を伝ってget's up 目を覚ましてよget's out もう間もなく
I'm going to die and die and die and die.
I'm going to die and die.
I'm going to die.
Let's start this world.
Even I can't outprop this world.
All I need is get just done.
We can catch the game.
We can't catch the game.
I don't know what I'm doing here.
I'm going to die.
Everyone is not going on.
We can't catch the game.
I'm one of the Black Bulls now.
Me.
Oh, Prince.
So many things have happened.
So much has changed since the day we met 500 years ago.
Why, hello there.
You must be Sekre, right?
I'm sorry.
I would have come to you, but I've been totally buried in my research lately.
So tell me about this magic of yours.
Ceiling magic?
I've never heard of that before.
It must be rare.
You're so lucky.
How can we put it to use?
Thinking about it is so exciting.
Magical tools?
That's right.
With these, even someone born without any magic can use all kinds of spells.
I think it'll be a good way to make our society more equal in the future.
Equal?
You're dreaming.
It can be done, with the help of my magic items.
I'm sure your ability will be a huge help in making them.
I know.
Can you seal magic into objects?
Um, yes.
Wow, really?
That's perfect!
And so, I helped the prince with his magical inventions.
I'd never met anyone else like him in my whole life.
There were some members of his family who resented him because of the progressive ideas that he'd champion.
But he didn't let that bother him.
He remained strong and honest, never compromising his beliefs.
I didn't know it then, but the prince associated was a group that was different than humans.
They were the elves, a race who was loved and blessed by mana, and who lived their lives in quiet peace.
Wow, I can't believe it!
Lit and his sword magic have been chosen by the four-leaf clover grimoire!
What's so exciting, Mom?
Well, you see, darling, only a select few were given a grimoire just like he got.
It even comes with an extra helping of luck.
Oh!
Licked in his four-leaf grimoire!
He's so cool!
The three leaves of the clover each stand for something.
One is integrity, one is hope, and one is love.
Good luck dwells within the fourth leaf.
And in the fifth leaf, there lives the devil.
Back then, we all assumed that was nothing but an old saying.
What do you think about all this?
Hmm?
You know, there's been a lot of talk about humans planning to attack us.
I'm sure it's a rumor.
It's still a possibility, though, isn't it?
I mean, think.
The human race is so wicked and mean-spirited,
they slaughter helpless animals just for the sport of it without giving it a second thought.
What's that thing?
What's he doing?
Sword magic.
Now, origin flash.
Light magic.
Lamp of Avior.
You're not hurt, are you?
No, I'm fine.
Thank you for saving me.
Tatia, don't leave the castle like that.
I'm sorry.
Besides, a wind magic user like you isn't supposed to be getting herself caught in a mana tornado.
What were you thinking?
Thank you for helping my sister.
It's no-
Phenomenal magic talent.
Similar ideals.
The same four-leaf grimoires.
For the first time, the prince had found a peer and licked the leader of the elves.
Let's foster understanding.
Your elvish mana really is a remarkable thing.
If we combine that with our own magic item technology,
this land will be safer and more prosperous.
Let's all work together, hand in hand.
By combining his work with the elves' resources,
the prince developed magic item technology ever further,
and the world he'd dreamed of where both races could live in harmony
was becoming a reality.
He and Licked were best friends,
and soon, they would become family as well.
Is it true?
You're with child?
With you for parents,
it'll be a lovely baby.
Hey, congrats, Tetya.
And you too, I guess.
Well, thank you for including me, Raya.
What are you pouting about, Tiny?
It's nothing.
You're still little.
You'll understand one day.
Would you shut up?
Stop talking down to me like I'm some stupid baby!
Excuse me then, big man.
Lumiere,
once I marry Tetya,
our families will be one,
and you and I will become brothers.
I'm sure some humans won't approve of that.
Probably.
But still, with your help,
we can create a new world of peace and equality.
I truly believe that.
I believe it too.
I know that you and I were brought together by destiny.
I'm sorry, Tetya,
but it looks like I might have to arrive late to your wedding.
Father has summoned me to the palace that day,
and I can't refuse.
I know you're disappointed that he and the others don't approve of this,
but please, don't worry.
I'm sure they'll come to understand someday.
Yes, and it's all right.
Even if you're late to the ceremony,
Licht and his family will be so pleased to see you there.
But,
it's likely that even then,
his plot was already in motion.
Why did Father call me here?
We didn't mention the wedding to anyone,
so it must be a coincidence.
I should hurry, or I'll miss it.
Oh, my goodness!
Good luck!
We wish you the best!
Congratulations!
Thank you all very much!
How sweet!
I want to be a bride.
I'm sure you'll meet your soulmate one day too, Fauna.
Yeah, and hopefully soon.
May the rest of your days be happy ones.
Thank you.
I wonder,
can we really come to understand each other like he said we could?
Licht believes it's possible.
Maybe they're right.
Elves and human beings,
living side by side.
I'm here, Father.
You wanted to speak with me?
Now, bye!
What's this?
I'm trapped!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Good day, my prince!
Minister?
No, that villainous mana doesn't belong to him.
Who are you?
Who, me?
Despair, hatred, disloyalty, death, any number of awful things, really.
Use whatever name you prefer.
I've read about this being a soul from the other world with evil mana.
A devil.
Where's my family?
Who knows?
Perhaps they've gone to confront that other race that's plotting to use your unwitting princess
to topple this entire kingdom.
But that's only a guess.
Imagine how surprised the elves will be
when a monster's act of human violence befalls that little wedding ceremony
that only you were supposed to know was happening.
No!
Let go!
As soon as I obtain my body in Grimoire,
I promise I'll come back to play with you again.
Wait!
Help me!
Isn't anyone here?
Please!
Prince!
Thank goodness!
Oh no!
What's that?
I've been trapped by a devil!
I knew you would never do such a thing!
I'm not sure why,
but the magic item we created was stolen!
Quick!
Use your sealing magic!
Of course!
Sealing magic!
Inverse release!
Come on!
Fly faster!
Tetya!
Licht!
Hold on!
What's going on?
It's the humans!
They're attacking us!
Everyone this way!
Let's hurry!
My spells won't work.
Our magic!
It's been sealed away!
Let's get down!
This is light magic.
Does that mean...
This is a mistake!
It's not true!
No way!
I won't accept it!
I'll never!
Forget you!
Are...
There's the device we made!
His items stored and distributed magic,
and their magic stones amplified spells by linking to another world.
That's a five-leaf grimoire!
I knew it.
Knew what?
Deep inside.
I knew you weren't responsible.
Please forgive me.
I should never have harbored any suspicion of you, not for a second.
You are the future we all believed in.
You represent hope.
What are you?
Right now, my body is filled with an overwhelming amount of negative mana.
I can't control myself, but we mustn't let that devil succeed.
No, Ligt.
In order to keep my body and power from falling under the influence of evil,
I've absorbed even more negative magic.
Stop it!
You can't do this!
I'm sorry, but I have one last selfish request.
And only you can grant it.
I beg of you.
There has to be another way!
Lumiere, I need you to kill me.
The devil manipulated Prince Lumiere and the elves in order to throw the owner of the four-leaf grimoire into a deep pit of despair.
He did so because it's the way a five-leaf grimoire is born,
which, in turn, allows the devil to manifest itself in this world,
along with his true form and ultimate powers.
Where did that creature come from?
Run away!
This must be the end of the world.
Now, I understand why I was born with such a massive amount of magic power.
Don't worry.
I won't let you become a murderer.
Who's that?
Look!
It's Prince Lumiere!
They stole something I helped create,
and used it to take away the elves' magic.
We built that item to make everyone's lives better.
I'm sorry, Prince.
Lady Tetia.
Is there anything left that I can do?
My friends!
This item is our legacy!
We can still make it a good one!
I'll use the item we built
to absorb his attack.
I should have known.
It couldn't withstand that much magic.
The beam's stopped!
That evil mana's fading!
Lumiere...
This is your chance.
Do it now.
I can't...
You're right.
I have to!
Let's go!
You may have prevented me from possessing him, but you put on a good show.
For the time being, I suppose I'll have to be satisfied with taking his grivoire.
Don't you dare! Stay away! I won't let you have it!
Magic stones!
You saw what happened to the elves, didn't you?
You're a mere human!
If you used those, you wouldn't be able to keep your form for even a tiny spell! Give up!
Never. I'll use these stones to maximize my power.
Sealing magic! Eternal prison!
Wait, I know what you're doing.
Sealing magic, eh?
Her suit presents a bit of a problem, but I can use the magic stones for reincarnation.
Come here.
What's happening?
There's even more despair and pain in store for the soul who possesses the four-leaf.
So I'll go ahead and sow the seeds for him.
Forbidden magic, no other pitch!
I'll be sure to work much more slowly and carefully next time, in an era where you two don't exist!
Ha ha ha!
Sekurei! Are you hurt?
You're alive!
You managed to seal that devil away.
Yes, it should contain him for a little while, but it won't hold out forever, so we...
No! Prince!
This is the way it should be.
I kept my promise to Ligt, so it's...
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'm going to use the magic stones to seal you.
It probably won't be perfect, but it should at least keep you alive.
If the devil's seal is broken, then the peaceful future we fought so hard for will be taken away.
Think about what you're doing, Sekurei.
If you use any more of that forbidden magic, your humanity's going to be lost forever.
That's better than letting you die here, your highness.
It's just as he said.
You're our hope for a brighter future.
When I finally woke up, several centuries had passed.
So the prince began his long slumber as a statue, and for some reason, I was turned into a bird.
I've been spared, but in the small form, I'll need help from the future mages.
That day, I felt the presence of a powerful hope.
A hope that could stand against that fearsome devil.
Two more for us, huh?
Oh, there's a good boy.
Are you brothers?
Same age, so possibly twins as well.
No, they're neither.
This one here is sweet and well-behaved,
and this one, well, he's a bit spirited.
Then there's the fact that they don't look a thing alike.
Hmm, you know.
Now, for this spirited little...
Ow!
A bit too spirited.
Asta, huh?
Well, you've had a tough beginning, but your worries are over.
As of today, boys, this will be your home.
Asta, and you know.
We'll be right back.